trustifyme.org 2019-05-06

# trustify-me - Page Site

## Information Collection

  * We collect information from you when you place an online order, or respond to a communication such as an email, or participate in another site feature.
  * When ordering we may ask you for your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, credit card information or any other required information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
  * Like many websites, we use "cookies" to improve your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

## Information Use

We may use the information we collect from you when you make a purchase, respond to a survey or marketing communication, visit the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To personalize your website experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To allow us to assist you further in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * To promote a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * If you have opted-in to receive our email newsletter, we may send you periodic emails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional email from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?" section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these emails.

## Information Protection

We apply a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is controlled behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of people who have special access rights to such systems, who are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. In addition, all sensitive/credit card information you supply is transmitted via 128-Bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases using a random 16-digit encryption code, to be only accessed as stated above. For your convenience on future orders, and to automate the monthly and/or annual recurring transaction process, you can store your credit card information longer than 60 days if you select the "Keep my payment method on file for easy checkout on future orders" box during checkout.

## Do we use "cookies"?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider stores on your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For example, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about website traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your web browser settings (such as Chrome or Internet Explorer). Please bear in mind, each browser is a little different. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting our support team.

## Information Disclosure To Third Parties

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include Trustify-me. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who support us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information private. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to abide by with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Remove Or Modify Information You Have Provided To Us

To modify your personal information please contact us via email. However, please note that we maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to fulfill that transaction and for record keeping.

## Third Party Links

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our website. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any opinion about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).

## Changes To Our Policy

If we decide to amend our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

## Questions and Feedback

We welcome your queries, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please forward any feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue via our ‘Contact Us’ page

## Online Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section regarding establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
